## Daffa Putera Kouseina, Mobile Developer

Purwokerto (Remote), Indonesia, +6281325218571, kouseinadaffa@gmail.com

LINKS	Portfolio, Github		
PROFILE	I'm a mobile developer. I have 3 years of experience in mobile development. I have built many Android and iOS with flutter framework. By working on those projects, I accrued an imposing skill set, which has taught me punctuality.		
EMPLOYMENT HISTORY			
Mar 2024 — Present	Mobile Developer, PT. Satu	Visi Raya (SAVIR)	Purwokerto
	As a Mobile Developer at Satu Visi Raya, I played a key role in developing and maintaining mobile app. My technical expertise in Flutter, enabled me to contribute to the team. I was involved in the full software development lifecycle, from concept to deployment, ensuring high-quality and efficient software solutions.		
Jul 2023 — Jul 2024	Mobile Developer, Dealjava		Medan
	methodology - Define git rules, folders, code, etc.	oment process through the entire software life cycle clogies such as Flutter, Bloc, Stream, Rest Api etooth and wireless	e under Waterfall
Oct 2021 — May 2023	Mobile Developer, PT. RAF	THASA ARTHA WISESA	Jakarta
	methodology - Define git rules, folders, code, etc Handling playstore, appstore, fire	ologies such as Flutter, Getx, Firebase, Git, Rest Ap	
Oct 2020 — Nov 2021	Software Engineer, Freelanc	e (Self employed)	Purwokerto
	<ul> <li>Create app for helps the growth o</li> <li>Health Services for Premature Babi</li> <li>Create news portal application, w</li> <li>Create application for ordering fo</li> <li>Create application to provide tou</li> </ul>	Fpremature babies on a regular basis, stores data diges.  nich contains about digital coins.  od online and has 2 applications, namely for orderiest information around Bandung.  nd out market in Lampung, with Java	
EDUCATION			
Oct 2023 — Present	Informatics Engineering, ST	MIK Widya Utama	Purwokerto
SKILLS	Flutter	Git	
	Kotlin	Playstore & Appstore	
	Java	Android & IOS	
HOBBIES	I would like to join tech competition like hackaton or something else. Such as codefest asia, permata youth preneur, invofest, etc.		